Alexandru Olteanu

Engineering Student

Contact

Address

Bucharest, B, 060042

Phone

+40 0729 868 263

E-mail

alexandruolteanu99@gmail.c

Skills

Website Development

Logo Designing

Marketing Research

Game Development

Teamwork

Flexible & Adaptable

Planning and Coordination

 Detail-Oriented Computer Science student with a comprehensive understanding of C++, C, HTML5, Wordpress and Shopify, intermediate experience with Python3 and a little bit of experience with Javascript. Excited to use my coding and debugging skills for new challenges!

Work History

2020-01 -2020-03

Developer Consultant

Landlord GO, Bucharest, B

- I helped at designing different concepts for Landlord GO game (menu customizations, character ideas, etc).
- I created the Short and Long description for the game available on both Android and IOS!
- · I designed different banners for game presentation!

2020-03 -Current

Freelancer

Fiverr, Upwork, Freelancer, Bucharest, B

 I started working as freelancer on different websites like Fiverr, Upwork, Freelancer a few months ago. I did website development with Wordpress and Shopify, logo designing, marketing research for my customers businesses and a little bit of video editing.

2020-05 -2020-06

Online Seller

Alexandru Olteanu, Bucharest, B

I created a brand new online shop from scratch that
was selling bands for home workouts. I choosed the
name "BandElite" for my store. I also did the video
add editing and marketing work. I thought that
based on Google Trends (bands search term
exploded during the pandemic), I will have great
success selling bands. Unfortunately, I didn't have
enough funds to promote my ads because I was
just starting building capital from my freelancing
activities.

Education

2020-10 -Current Engineering Student: Automatic Control And Computer Science

Faculty Of Computer Science - Bucharest

Accomplishments

- I qualified every year of high-school for interregional informatics olympiad in high-school!
- I qualified for national informatics olympiad, taking second place in previous phase!
- I got great results in multiple programming competitions organized on Codeforces, Hackerrank and Codechef!